propertyupdate.com.au 2011-11-24

# Disclaimer, Refunds & Privacy Information

Disclaimer

The information provided on this website is for use of a general nature only and is not intended to be relied upon as, nor to be a substitute for, specific professional or investment advice. 

No responsibility for loss occasioned to any persons acting on or refraining from action as a result of any material in this publication can be accepted. Readers should seek professional advice from suitably qualified professionals regarding their own specific needs.

Returns and Refund Policy

**Return of faulty goods:** If any product is received in faulty, non-working or damaged condition we will exchange the item at no cost to the customer. Please email us with the order number that you were provided, so that we can arrange for the goods to be collected. 

**Returns on non-faulty goods:** We believe all our products represent quality and value for money and therefore do not give refunds on non faulty items. 

If you are unable to attend a seminar or workshop your payment will be credited for a future workshop or towards other goods available at our online store.

Privacy Statement

We recognise the importance of privacy protection. Our policy for dealing with any personal information that you might disclose to us while visiting this website is explained below.

The type of personal information that we collect from you will depend on how you use our website. You can be certain that the information we receive about you will be treated as strictly confidential.

The names of persons who subscribe to our newsletter are added to our database and will be sent regular property updated by email. We will also inform you of upcoming events.

Your name will never be given to a third party. You can always unsubscribe if you wish.

**The personal information we collect when you log onto this site, how we do it and what we do with it:**

If you log onto the website and read or download information our Internet Service Provider/Hosting Provider, will record your server address, domain name, the date and time of your visit to our site, the pages viewed and the information downloaded. This information is used for statistical and web site development purposes only.

**The circumstances under which we disclose information about you:**

It is our policy not to sell or pass on any personal information that you may have provided. An exception to this is where we may be required by law to disclose certain information.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and would like to know your options in relation to not having this information used by these companies, please contact us. 

**Purchases:**

When purchasing products and services via our websites, you will be billed by Metropole Education Services Pty Ltd and your credit card details and related personal information will be processed by third party payment processor and its secure servers. The name of the payment processor will be disclosed to you in the payment process.

Please refer to Third Party Payment Processor for details of their privacy policy.

Our website contains links to this and other web sites which our privacy policy does not apply. Our Privacy Policy cannot be extend beyond our domain, and web pages therein.

**How we handle emails:**

We will preserve the contents of any e-mail message that you send us if we believe that we have a legal requirement to do so.

**What to do if you believe the information we hold about you is inaccurate:**

If you believe that any information that we hold about you is inaccurate or out of date, please contact us and we will review the relevant information.

**How to contact us if you wish to discuss this policy:**

If you wish to discuss any aspect of this policy please contact us at [info@metropole.com.au](mailto:info@metropole.com.au)
